{"questions":[
    {"questiontext":"Which of the following is used to ensure integrity?",
        "answerchoice1":"MD5",
        "answerchoice2":"Authentication",
        "answerchoice3":"AES",
        "answerchoice4":"Encryption",
        "answer":1},

    {"questiontext":"If an individual is involved in an ethical dilemma where there is conflict between the (ISC)2 canons, how should the conflict be resolved?",
        "answerchoice1":"It is not possible to have a conflict between the cannons",
        "answerchoice2":"The preamble should take precedence",
        "answerchoice3":"The (ISC)2 peer review panel should queried",
        "answerchoice4":"Conflicts between the canons should be resolved in the order of the cannons",
        "answer":4},

    {"questiontext":"Members who violate any provision of the (ISC)2 Code of Ethics may be subject to revocation of certification. Who makes this determination?",
        "answerchoice1":"The (ISC)2 board of trustees",
        "answerchoice2":"The (ISC)2 Code of Ethics review board",
         "answerchoice3":"A peer review panel",
         "answerchoice4":"A court of law",
        "answer":3},

    {"questiontext":"What are the three main goals of any information security program?",
        "answerchoice1":"Preventing losses in accounting, integrity, and confidentiality",
        "answerchoice2":"Preventing losses in availability, identification, and confidentiality",
        "answerchoice3":"Preventing losses in availability, integrity, and due care",
        "answerchoice4":"Preventing losses in availability, integrity, and confidentiality",
        "answer":4},

    {"questiontext":"Which of the following describes preventing the loss of confidentiality?",
        "answerchoice1":"Protecting disclosure of data from unauthorized users",
        "answerchoice2":"Protecting disclosure of data from authorized users",
        "answerchoice3":"Ensuring that the data hasn't been modified",
        "answerchoice4":"Ensuring that users can access the data when it's needed",
        "answer":1},

    {"questiontext":"Which of the following provides a layered approach to security?",
        "answerchoice1":"Security triad",
        "answerchoice2":"Nonrepudiation",
        "answerchoice3":"AAAs",
        "answerchoice4":"Defense in depth",
        "answer":4},

    {"questiontext":"You want to ensure that a system can identify individual users, track their activity, and log their actions. What does this provide?",
        "answerchoice1":"Accountability",
        "answerchoice2":"Availability",
        "answerchoice3":"Authentication",
        "answerchoice4":"Authorization",
        "answer":1},

    {"questiontext":"What are the three A's (AAA) of information security?",
        "answerchoice1":"Authentication, Availability, and Authorization",
        "answerchoice2":"Account, Authentication, and Availability",
        "answerchoice3":"Authentication, Authorization, and Accounting",
        "answerchoice4":"Availability, Availability, and Authorization",
        "answer":3},

    {"questiontext":"You want to ensure that users sending email are not able to deny sending it. What is this called?",
        "answerchoice1":"Audit logging",
        "answerchoice2":"Due care",
        "answerchoice3":"Authentication",
        "answerchoice4":"Nonrepudiation",
        "answer":4},

    {"questiontext":"Which of the following is used to validate an e-commerce transaction?",
        "answerchoice1":"Least privilege",
        "answerchoice2":"Identification",
        "answerchoice3":"Signature",
        "answerchoice4":"Nonrepudiation",
        "answer":1},

    {"questiontext":"An organization grants users access only to system resources that they need to perform their job. What principle is this?",
        "answerchoice1":"Least privilege",
        "answerchoice2":"Separation of duties",
        "answerchoice3":"Authentication",
        "answerchoice4":"Due care",
        "answer":1},

    {"questiontext":"Which of the following is a security principle designed to prevent fraud by ensuring that job responsibilities are divided?",
        "answerchoice1":"Defense in depth",
        "answerchoice2":"Separation of duties",
        "answerchoice3":"Authentication",
        "answerchoice4":"Nonrepudiation",
        "answer":2},

    {"questiontext":"An organization has a responsibility to investigate risks associated with new purchases.  What is this?",
        "answerchoice1":"Due diligence",
        "answerchoice2":"Due care",
        "answerchoice3":"Due process",
        "answerchoice4":"Nonrepudiation",
        "answer":1},

    {"questiontext":"What is due care?",
        "answerchoice1":"Implementing security policies and procedures to protect resources",
        "answerchoice2":"Eliminate risk",
        "answerchoice3":"Don't need due care over PII",
        "answerchoice4":"Organizations can be sued if they fail to exercise due care over resources such as customer data",
        "answer":1}
]}
